let questions = [
  {
    question: "What is the original name given to the blood elves?",
    answers: ["Quil'dorei", "Kel'dorei", "Sin'dorei"],
    correctAnswer: 2,
  },

  {
    question:
      "Dalaran once rested in Silverpine Forest before being transported to Northrend",
    answers: ["True", "False"],
    correctAnswer: 1,
  },

  {
    question:
      "The curse of flesh was the cause behind the creation of the dwarves",
    answers: ["True", "False"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },

  {
    question:
      "The Four Horsemen consist of which four bosses during the Naxxramas raid?",
    answers: [
      "Thane Korth'azz, Lady Blauemox, Baron Rivendare and Sir Zeliek",
      "Lady Blauemox, Darion Mograine, Lord Malakriez and Teron Gorefiend",
      "Baron Rivendare, Darion Mograine, Teron Gorefiend and Scourgelord Tyrannus",
      "Teron Gorefiend, Sir Zeliek, Lord Malakriez and Lady Blauemox",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },

  {
    question:
      "Onyxia used to spy on  Stormwind in  the guise of a chief advisor. What did she call herself while under her human form",
    answers: [
      "Lady Katirina Preston",
      "Lady Katrana Prestor",
      "Magistrix Lauville Karnos",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 1,
  },

  {
    question:
      "Which of the following is the only raid in world of warcraft where you can play a game of  chess?",
    answers: [
      "The Steamvaults",
      "The Gamevaults",
      "Boardgame Land",
      "Karazhan",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
  },

  {
    question:
      "What was the purpose of the blood elven expedition in bloodmist isle?",
    answers: [
      "To create a portal to Outland so they could travel through it.",
      "To assassinate the draenei leader.",
      "To summon an army of demons to overwhelm the Exodar.",
      "To find a crystal that would allow them to communicate with Kael'thas.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },

  {
    question:
      "Which of these quotes is NOT spoken by Onyxia in the raid 'Onyxia's Lair'",
    answers: [
      "'I am tired of this meaningless exertion! I shall incinerate you all from above!'",
      "'How fortuitous, normally i have to leave my lair in order to feed!'",
      "'Whelps, many whelps! NOW, handle it!!!'",
      "Arrogant fools, I shall enjoy feasting upon your charred flesh!'",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
  },

  {
    question: "Which company publishes 'World of Warcraft'?",
    answers: [
      "Sierra Entertainment",
      "Blizzard Entertainment",
      "Rockstar Games",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 1,
  },

  {
    question: "What species are most characters in the game?",
    answers: ["Human", "Night elf", "Dwarf"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },

  {
    question: "What year was 'World of Warcraft' released?",
    answers: [2004, 2005, 2006],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },

  {
    question:
      "What is NOT a secondary skill your character can learn during gameplay?",
    answers: ["Leathercraft", "Fishing", "First aid"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },

  {
    question: "Which is NOT a continent in the Eastern Kingdoms?",
    answers: ["Khaz Modan", "Azeroth", "Kalimdor"],
    correctAnswer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "The auction house has about how many trades every day?",
    answers: ["1.2 million", "1.5 million", "3 million"],
    correctAnswer: 2,
  },

  {
    question: "'World of Warcraft' has roughly how many subscribers?",
    answers: ["8.7 million", "5.6 milliom", "7.2 million"],
    correctAnswer: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the Chinese copycat game that looks suspiciously similar to 'World of Warcraft'?",
    answers: ["World of Fight", "World of Warriors", "World of Sorcery"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },

  {
    question: "What was the first expansion added to 'World of Warcraft'?",
    answers: ["Cataclysm", "The Burning Crusade", "Wrath of the Lich King"],
    correctAnswer: 1,
  },

  {
    question:
      "Up to how many adventurers can a typical dungeon accommodate at one time?",
    answers: ["Seven", "Six", "Five"],
    correctAnswer: 2,
  },

  {
    question: "At its peak, the game had how many monthly subscribers?",
    answers: ["20 million", "15 million", "12 million"],
    correctAnswer: 2,
  },

  {
    question:
      "'World of Warcraft' is played in approximately how many countries?",
    answers: [244, 159, 132],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },

  {
    question: "Which faction in the game is the most popular with players?",
    answers: ["The Alliance", "The Horde", "Neutral"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },

  {
    question:
      "About how many online accounts have been created since the release of 'World of Warcraft'?",
    answers: ["71 million", "83 million", "100 million"],
    correctAnswer: 2,
  },

  {
    question: "How many original classes are there in the game?",
    answers: ["Nine", "Eight", "Eleven"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },

  {
    question: "The event known as The Shattering happened in which expansion?",
    answers: ["Cataclysm", "Wrath of the Lich King", "Mists of Pandaria"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },

  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the enormous storm in the middle of the game's world?",
    answers: ["The Tempest", "The Maelstrom", "The Chaos"],
    correctAnswer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Which two races fought in the First War?",
    answers: ["Humans and trolls", "Humans and orcs", "Humans and elves"],
    correctAnswer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the most common pet in the game?",
    answers: ["Cat", "Squirrel", "Dog"],
    correctAnswer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Which race descended from dark trolls?",
    answers: ["Gnomes", "Night elves", "Undead"],
    correctAnswer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the most popular profession in the game?",
    answers: ["Mining", "Alchemy", "Blacksmithing"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
];

export default questions;
